<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Rachel Pehrsson</title>
    <link>https://rachelpehrsson.github.io/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Rachel Pehrsson</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 23:36:08 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rachelpehrsson.github.io/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Quiz</title>
      <link>https://rachelpehrsson.github.io/projects/dynamicquiz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 23:36:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rachelpehrsson.github.io/projects/dynamicquiz/</guid>
      <description>My Distinguished Major Project at the University of Virginia was a dynamic quiz system that adjusted practice content based on interaction with the student. It addressed a problem within the computer science department at the University of Virginia, as well as other institutions; the department classroom size is scaling, but the number of TA’s is not expanding at the same rate. Therefore, it is important to test whether certain aspects of personalized help can be automated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Food for the Fourth</title>
      <link>https://rachelpehrsson.github.io/projects/foodforthefourth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 21:56:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rachelpehrsson.github.io/projects/foodforthefourth/</guid>
      <description>Food for the Fourth is an organization I founded in 2019 to promote increased donation to food banks in America. For the website, I wanted to make something simple yet eye-catching that would quickly get our point across, but could be easily expanded as the organization grew. I decided to make the website a one-pager for the time being, with the navigation bar transitioning between different sections of the page. I designed the website in Illustrator before I started working.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Decoding Nutrition Labels</title>
      <link>https://rachelpehrsson.github.io/projects/nutritiontutor/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 22:28:30 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rachelpehrsson.github.io/projects/nutritiontutor/</guid>
      <description>Decoding Nutrition Labels is a rule-based cognitive tutor for teaching 6th graders to read nutrition labels on food and glean information about nutrient content. It was built using CTAT, a cognitive tutor authoring tool developed at Carnegie Mellon written in Nools.js.
We based our design on a worksheet that helped students decode nutrition labels and then confirmed the process with a nutrition expert. We used the worksheet in a Cognitive Task Analysis (CTA) using 6th grade students and others who had never read an American nutrition label (international students) in order to determine their pain points and preferences.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
